# **JAMES LEWIS**

6/126 Mitchell Street, Brunswick East · 0422732175 Jamesglew@gmail.com · LinkedIn Profile · Github

Junior software developer with a passion for user centered design principles. I aim to provide the best possible experience for users and the client.

### EXPERIENCE

### August 2021 - Present

JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER, PING Co.

Junior frontend developer working with React and Material UI.

#### June 2021 - August 2021

UI/UX AND FRONTEND DEVELOPER, UNEEK

CONTRACTOR

Frontend and UI/UX development using React, Typescript and Material UI.

#### February **2020 - November 2020**

UI/UX AND FRONTEND DEVELOPER, DIGITIZATION OF ABORIGINAL HISTORY PROJECT

UI/UX DESIGNER

User experience designer for final year project.

## FRONT END DEVELOPER

Front end development using android studio and kotlin.

## **JANUARY 2015 - SEPTEMBER 2016**

FIBRE OPTIC NETWORK DESIGNER, BIARRI NETWORKS

PRODUCT TESTING

PROJECT PLANNING & TEAM LEADERSHIP

**CLIENT LIAISON** 

## **EDUCATION**

## FEBRUARY 2021

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE, SWINBURNE UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY Majoring in Software Development and co-majoring in Cyber Security

## November 2014

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, SWINBURNE UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

Majoring in Biochemistry and co-majoring in Advanced Chemistry

# **S**KILLS

- Kotlin
- C++/C#
- Python
- CSS/HTML
- UI/UX Design
- Material UI
- Git
- Agile Development
- SQL Databases
- Android Development
- React
- Redux

## REFERENCES

References will be provided if requested.

- Project Management
- Team Leadership Experience
- Technical Writing & Presentation
- Client Relations
- GIS Data Systems
- Cisco Certified Network Associate
- 120 WPM Typing Speed